CV - Victor Fabricio Zubieta Chambi - Semi-Senior Quality Control Engineer

CABA - Buenos Aires, MOM 2987 • fabricio.zubieta@gmail.com • fabriciozubieta.github.io

Summary

Quality Control Engineer with over 10 years of experience, I specialize in manual testing and quality assurance, playing a key role in the success of complex projects from a technical view. I worked in Agile Methodologies like Scrum and Kanban, and have strong skills in test case development and execution. I am committed to teamwork, adaptability, and delivering innovative software solutions following ISTQB standards.

Education

INSTITUTE FOR HIGHER TECHNICAL EDUCATION № 21

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Technical Degree in Information Systems Analysis, 7/10

August 2023

Relevant Coursework: Systems Programming, Data Structures, Database Management, Web Application Development.

TECHNICAL EDUCATION SCHOOL No. 1 Otto Krause

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Electronics Technician, orientation in Telecommunications.

December 2008

- Electronic specialty representative at the 1st Technical Schools Fair.

Relevant Experience

GLOBANT - Semi-Senior Quality Control Engineer

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Client: Triumph Financial - My Triumph Next

February - Present 2024

I worked to the migration of the new version of the web and mobile application focusing on the seamless integration of new features across all platforms. This role involved developing and executing full functional test cases, while also performing daily automated testing and generating detailed reports of the results.

GLOBANT - Semi-Senior Quality Control Engineer

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Client: Deloitte - Cyber Compliance

April 2023 - January 2024

Ensured cyber compliance in the Deloitte project in Qlik Sense by developing and executing SQL queries for data verification, utilizing test cases to ensure the accuracy and security of the information across multiple data sources (Excel reports, API, SQL Data bases).

ACCIONA IT - Semi-Senior QA Analyst

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Client: Comafi Bank - OpenBanking

April 2021 - April 2022

Conducted functional testing of APIs for new banking services at Banco Comafi, ensuring that all endpoints met the required specifications and performance standards for a seamless user experience.

Technical Skills & Projects

Programming: Assembly, C, Java, Python, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Ai Prompting.

Languages: Spanish - Native, English - B1, Japanese - N5

Tools: Azure DevOps, JIRA, Confluence, Postman, Swagger, Splunk, AS-400, Azure Data Studio, Power BI, Looker Studio, Git, CLI, ChatGPT.

Automation of API Testing with Postman

Implemented a series of automated API tests using Postman, covering a comprehensive range of endpoints for a financial services project.

Social App - Final Project for Degree

Developed a social networking app that enables users to create profiles, share updates. The project involved the full development cycle, from designing the user interface to implementing backend services and ensuring secure data handling. Technologies used include Python, Flask Framework for the frontend and backend, and MySQLite for data storage.

Leadership Experience

TSOFT - Semi-Senior Quality Control Engineer

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Client: NEC - NECSIS Security System

April 2016 - March 2017

Led the testing efforts for the NECSIS security system, focusing on functional and integration testing with biometric validation. Developed and executed test cases to ensure secure and seamless integration across all components, while coordinating with cross-functional teams.

CDA INFORMATICA - Semi-Senior Quality Control Engineer

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Client: Red Link S.A. - National Bank of Argentina (BNA+)

August 2019 - April 2021

Led the integration and functional testing for the Virtual Wallet app and its backend systems. Conducted web and mobile testing (Android/iOS), ensuring compliance with banking regulations. Developed and executed test cases, supported effort estimation, and managed testing across databases, applications, and web services.